間違いない。
これは...
陰謀
陰謀だ！
そうだ、俺は...
俺は大きな陰謀に...
陰謀の...
途轍もなく巨大な陰謀に...
A dream and a conspiracy...
陰謀に...
巻き込まれてしまったのだ!
...magical girl, that is me!
どうも（？）最近頭の調子は悪い...
一日１６時間も寝ているからだろうか?
隣の部屋からは今日も美少女のアニメ主題歌がガンガン流れてくる。
先月辺りから毎日だ
分かってるよ
もう何百回となく聞いたフレーズだ
しかしプリリンってネーミングはどうなんだ？
プルプルしてる女の子ってか？
それは人間じゃねだろう！
プリンみたいな女の子って意味か？
喧しい！
うるさい！
今日という今日は限界だ！
好きでもない歌を永遠と聞かされるのは精神衛生上よくない！
抗議に行ってやる！
なんてことはない。
簡単なことだ。
ドアを開けて、隣の部屋へまでほんの何歩か歩くだけ
そしてノックをして、ドアを開けて…
このアニオタ！うるせぇんだよ！
と、怒鳴りつけてやればいい。
それだけの話だ。
たった…それだけのことなんだ…
ちょっとおかしいんじゃない？
声が聞こえた…
恥ずかしくないのかしら
気持ち悪いわよね！
馬鹿みたい。
ちょっと歩かないでほしいわ！
マジキモイ！
うっぜぇんだよ！
勘弁してくれよ！
大学一年の夏。
くそ熱いな、学校に向かっている途中だった。
俺は、逃げるようにアパートへと引き返した。
そして、その日から外出するのを止めた。
園芸三昧。
今日のテーマは、セイタカアワダチソウ
陰謀...
陰謀... 陰謀... 陰謀...
陰謀?!
この世界には陰謀が存在するの。
コロンビア号...
そう、あの人もそう言っていた。
茶髪は...
That's right, the existence of conspiracy is talked about in society as if it were true.
Cedar pollen is the facial tissue industry's conspiracy...
でも、先輩…
陰謀とされているものの９９％はただの妄想。
もしくは意図的な大嘘。
つまりはデタラメなんです。
じゃ、１％は本物ってこと？
後輩がいじめに遭っていた。
中等部の生徒。
先輩にいいところを見せたかった。
陰謀...
おい、やめろよ！
陰謀... 陰謀...
教えてください、先輩。
これも何かの陰謀ですか？
私語をやめて！
ホームルームは終わってません！
静かに！
おめぇが一番うるせぇよ！
佐藤くん！
言いたいことがあるなら、挙手して言ってよ！
あれも、陰謀？
これも、陰謀…
これも…
これも！
全ては陰謀ですか？
夢と陰謀の
魔法少女
陰謀!
そうだ！
俺は確率わずか１％以下の本物の陰謀に巻き込まれてしまったんだ！
おめでとう、佐藤君！
ようやく気づいたんだね！
あ...
物事が何一つも上手くいかないのは
全て君を引き込ませるための陰謀だったんだよ！
だが、誰がそんな陰謀を？
陰謀電波だ！
どうしたんだいテレビくん？
N.H.K.よ！
悪の秘密結社、N.H.K.からの攻撃よ！
N.H.K.?
そうか！
どうして今までこんな簡単なことに気付かなかったのだろう？
アニメと言えばオタク。
オタクと言えば人付き合いが苦手だろう。
そういう人間はえとして（？）引きこもりがちになる。People like that eventually become reclusive.
In other words,
they have been mass-producing anime otaku by showing them interesting anime,
helping to create a massive emergence of NEETs!
Basically, N.H.K.とは...
日本
引きこもり
協会
日本 引きこもり 協会!
I am the man who became aware of the N.H.K.'s conspiracy:
Sato Tatsuhiro, 22 years old!
I've shut myself away from society for three years...
Almost four years now!
Some karate masters would seclude themselves in the mountains
in order to master the secret technique that could break rocks.
If I can obtain strength by secluding myself,
I should have cultivated enough strength to crush this beer bottle by now.
Who broke the beer bottle?
It was me!
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts! Where's the first aid kit?
Oww!
Oh, before that, I'd better do something about these shards!
Come on, calm down!
First I have to clean up the shards, then treat this wound and...
Get lost! I'm too busy right now!
First of all, I'm a NEET!
Why would a NEET randomly make an appearance anyway?
Wait, could it be the utility bill collector?
Damn, I haven't sent them money for a while.
If they turn off my electricity,
I won't be able to live my NEET life comfortably anymore!
That's a big problem!
Y-Yes!
Jeez, I know they heard me!
Coming!
Huh?
Oh! I didn't know you were in there!
We're sorry to bother you, but...
A-Are you all right?
Your face is bleeding!
I-I-I'm fine.
O-Okay...
Oh, we've been distributing this pamphlet for free.
The Time is Already Here!
Wake up! "Hikikomori" Special Report.
NEET Population on the Rise
Are You Okay?
It's this month's special article.
Have you ever heard of NEETs before?
It's about the people who shut themselves away from society, refusing to go to school or work.
It's become a serious social issue these days...
Does this lady know that I've been shutting myself away from society?
Is it possible that I'm a well-known NEET in this town?
Is that it?!
Would you be interested in this?
If so, please take a look at it and...
Me? A NEET?! Give me a break!
All right, supposedly I haven't talked to anyone for almost a year.
Yeah, I dropped out of the college because of my social withdrawal trait!
And of course I'm unemployed!
To make matters worse, I have no hope for the future!
Yeah, right!
"Are you okay?"
Hell yeah, I'm okay, thank you very much!
I...
No one would go through this pain if a little prayer could fix it!
What can you possibly understand about it,
when I can't understand a damn thing about it myself!
You would never understand it!
Misaki! Come on, let's go.
What are you doing?
Misaki!
As a matter of fact, I do know what I should be doing about it.
I should get out there right now and find a part-time job or anything.
And if I did that, that rumor about a NEET living in this room would be just a lie.
Then, I'm sure that girl would think I just happened to be home because I was off today too.
Misaki...
I've got a handkerchief, pocket tissues, my wallet and my resume.
I've heard that you guys are hiring... I've heard that you guys are hiring...
I've heard that you guys are hiring...
All right!
Excuse me, um...
I've heard that... you...
you...
You?
You...
"I've heard that you..." What?
Y-Y-You...
You like motorcycles? I do!
You can become the wind, you know. There's nothing like the sound of that engine!
Wanna go for a ride together? What do you think?
But to tell you the truth, I've never even ridden a bike before! Yup!
Err...
Okay, bye.
I'm gonna kill myself!
But I already know that I can't kill myself like this.
Because I'll just pass out
and my grip will weaken before I die.
Why was she, of all girls, there?
Should a servant of God be working a part-time job?
No, I guess even a servant of God needs money.
After all, she's just flesh and blood.
That's right, she's flesh and blood.
I shouldn't! I shouldn't be doing this!
No!
I shouldn't!
God is watching me!
Now that I think about it,
there's no way the utility company would actually send someone to my house
to collect outstanding bills from me nowadays.
So, ignoring this won't affect my life in any way.
In fact, I should ignore it.
Because I carelessly opened the door yesterday,
I was... I was...
That girl...
RESUME ENCLOSED
Did she come all the way to drop this off for me?
To Tatsuhiro Sato,
You have been chosen for my project.
Therefore, please come to Mita Park on 4th Street at 9:00 tonight,
Misaki Nakahara.
If this is about soliciting me for her religion, she's not doing a good job at all.
It's hard to believe anyone would fall for this.
But at the same time, this is how they get you.
Using young girls to lure young men...
It's an old trick.
She must be a promiscuous girl.
Why would I fall for a girl like that?
Sato!
Come to me, Sato.
This is ridiculous!
Please come to Mita Park on 4th Street at 9:00 tonight,
Actually, that park is the only place I can relax outside of this room.
And I was thinking about going to the park to relax tonight.
I shouldn't let some bizarre letter like that interfere with my schedule.
That's right.
I was already planning to go to the park!
I realized that I overlooked one big possibility in all this.
It's possible that the letter was just a joke.
If that's the case, I'm the biggest clown for being here right now.
What am I saying?!
I was already planning to come here anyway!
Why did you run away this afternoon?
I was going to hire you right then and there because we've been short-staffed.
Did you get scared of going outside and working?
Since you're a hikikomori?
But I'm sure you'll be fine.
Because I know how to get you out of it.
Huh?
Besides, I've known about you for a long time.
I've come to rescue you.
Project
Episode 01
Welcome to the Project!
I mustn't run away!
This is Hitomi's request.
You can write the script, can't you?!
Next Episode
Welcome to the Creator!